A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller gubernatorial records, Office Subject Files, Third Administration, Subseries 37.3 FA439B
Rockefeller Archive Center
Nelson A. Rockefeller gubernatorial records, Office Subject Files, Third Administration, Subseries 37.3
1967-1970
Rockefeller Archive Center
New York (State). Governor (1959-1973: Rockefeller)
Rockefeller, Nelson A. (Nelson Aldrich)
FA439B
1.15 Cubic Feet 115 16mm microfilm reels.
Scope and Contents
Major subjects contained in the files include:
Administration. Aging. Agriculture. Authorities and Commissions. Banking. Civil Defense. Commemorative Observance. Conservation. Consumers. Correction. Disasters. Discrimination. Education. Executive Clemency. Extradition. Fiscal. Fund raising. Government. Health & Sanitation. Honorary Designation. Horse Racing. Housing. Insurance. Investigations. Invitations. Judiciary. Labor. Law. Legislation. Licensing. Mental Hygiene. Military and Naval. Organizations. Parks and Recreation facilities. Personnel Administration. Politics. Property. Public Safety. Public Utilities. Public Works. Regrets. Resignations and Vacancies. Statements. Transportation. Veterans. Welfare. Youth.
Conditions Governing Access
Microfilm user copies are open for research. The archival material has been reformatted. Access to the original paper records is restricted.
Arrangement
Series 37 is arranged into 4 subseries:
Subseries 1: First Administration, 1959-1962. Subseries 2: Second Administration, 1963-1966. Subseries 3: Third Administration, 1967-1970. Subseries 4: Fourth Administration, 1971-1973.
Material is arranged alphabetically by subject within each subseries.
Other Finding Aids
Other available finding aid for Nelson A. Rockefeller gubernatorial records, Office Subject Files, Series 37 include:
FA439 Nelson A. Rockefeller gubernatorial records, Office Subject Files, First Administration, Series 37.1
FA439A Nelson A. Rockefeller gubernatorial records, Office Subject Files, Second Administration, Series 37.2
FA439C Nelson A. Rockefeller gubernatorial records, Office Subject Files, Fourth Administration, Series 37.4
- Third Administration, 1967-1970; 3; 115 microform reels 115 microfilm reels.
  - Administration (Reel 1, Reel 2, Reel 3, Reel 4, Reel 5)
    - Executive Chamber (Reel 1, Reel 2, Reel 3)
      - Cabinet (Reel 1, Frame 25)
      - Governor's Itinerary (Reel 1)
      - Equipment (Reel 1, Frame 54)
      - Inauguration Invitations (Reel 1, Frame 56)
      - Inauguration (Reel 1, Frame 130)
      - Legislative Mail Reports (Reel 1, Frame 156)
      - Chamber Mailing List (Reel 2, Frame 16)
      - Personnel Appointments (Reel 2, Frame 39)
      - Personnel Staff Memos (Reel 2, Frame 48)
      - Personnel General (Reel 2, Frame 54)
      - Press Conference (Reel 2, Frame 72)
      - Press Releases (Reel 2, Frame 98)
      - Purchases (Reel 2, Frame 98)
      - Records General (Reel 2, Frame 102)
      - Women's Unit (Reel 2, Frame 127)
      - General (Reel 2, Frame 175)
      - Mansion (Reel 2, Frame 196)
      - General
        - Awareness Program (Reel 2, Frame 213)
        - Economic Opportunity Act (Reel 2, Frame 224)
        - Executive Order (Reel 3, Frame 16)
        - Memos to Dept. & Agen. Hds (Reel 3, Frame 38)
    - State, Department of (Reel 3)
      - Bingo Control Commission (Reel 3, Frame 53)
      - Athletic Commission (Reel 3, Frame 61)
      - General (Reel 3, Frame 69)
    - General (Reel 3, Reel 4, Reel 5)
      - Council on Architects (Reel 3, Frame 86)
      - Trips, 1969 March 1-1970 December (Reel 3, Frame 98)
      - Trips, 1967 November 20-1969 February 28 (Reel 4)
      - Trips, 1967 January 1-November 19 (Reel 5, Frame 15)
      - General (Reel 5, Frame 100)
  - Aging (Reel 5, Reel 6)
    - Problems of (Reel 5, Reel 6)
      - Employment (Reel 5, Frame 153)
      - Governor's Conference on Aging (Reel 5, Frame 154)
      - Housing (Reel 5, Frame 198)
      - Office of Aging (Reel 5, Frame 202)
      - Pensions & Social Securities (Reel 5, Frame 212)
      - Tax Exemption (Reel 5, Frame 213)
      - White House Conference on the Aging (Reel 5, Frame 237)
      - General (Reel 6, Frame 13)
  - Agriculture (Reel 6)
    - Agriculture and Markets (Reel 6)
      - Department of Animal Industry (Reel 6)
        - General (Reel 6, Frame 47)
        - Humane Slaughter (Reel 6, Frame 61)
      - Agriculture Fairs (Reel 6)
        - Department of New York State Fairs (Reel 6, Frame 72)
        - General (Reel 6, Frame 89)
      - Food Control (Reel 6)
        - Department of Meat (Reel 6, Frame 127)
          - General (Reel 6, Frame 135)
      - General (Reel 6, Frame 142)
    - Products (Reel 6)
      - Grapes (Reel 6, Frame 156)
      - Milk (Reel 6, Frame 176)
      - A-Z (Reel 6, Frame 196)
      - General (Reel 6, Frame 206)
  - Authorities and Commissions (Reel 6, Reel 7, Reel 8, Reel 9, Reel 10, Reel 11, Reel 12, Reel 13, Reel 14)
    - Apppointments Made (Reel 6)
      - City University Construction Fund (Reel 6, Frame 221)
    - American Revolution Bicentennial Commission (Reel 6, Frame 228)
    - Atomic and Space Development Authority (Reel 6, Reel 7)
      - 1970 July-December (Reel 6, Frame 240)
      - 1968 January-1970 June (Reel 7, Frame 17)
    - Bethpage Park Authority (Reel 7, Frame 84)
    - Bridge Authority (Reel 7, Frame 91)
    - Buffalo & Fort Erie Public Bridge Authority (Reel 7, Frame 97)
    - Buffalo Sewer Authority (Reel 7, Frame 98)
    - Delaware River Basin Commission (Reel 7, Frame 121)
    - Dormitory Authority (Reel 7, Frame 155)
    - Erie County Water Authority (Reel 7, Frame 170)
    - Health and Mental Hygiene Facility Improvement Corporation (Reel 7, Reel 8)
      - 1968 July-1970 (Reel 7, Frame 174)
      - 1968 January-June (Reel 8, Frame 14)
    - Hudson River Valley Commission (Reel 8, Frame 32)
    - Job Development Authority (Reel 8, Frame 80)
    - Jones Beach State Parkway Authority (Reel 8, Frame 104)
    - Liquor Authority (Reel 8, Frame 113)
    - Manhattan & Bronx Transit Operations Authority (Reel 8, Frame 182)
    - Mental Hygiene Improvement Fund (Reel 8, Reel 9)
      - 1967 September-1968 June (Reel 8, Frame 100)
      - 1967 January-August (Reel 9, Frame 14)
    - Metropolitan Transit Authority (Reel 9, Frame 38)
    - Monroe County Water Authority (Reel 9, Frame 67)
    - Nassau County Bridge Authority (Reel 9, Frame 75)
    - New York City Housing Authority (Reel 9, Frame 87)
    - New York City Transit Authority (Reel 9, Frame 120)
    - Niagara Frontier Port Authority (Reel 9)
      - 1967 May-1969 December (Reel 9, Frame 122)
      - 1967 January-April (Reel 10, Frame 14)
    - Ogdensburg Bridge & Port Authority (Reel 10, Frame 39)
    - Port of New York Authority Meetings (Reel 10, Reel 11, Reel 12)
      - 1969 November 13-1970 December 10 (Reel 10, Frame 58)
      - 1968 April 11-1969 October 9 (Reel 11)
      - 1967 January 12-1968 March 27 (Reel 12, Frame 15)
      - General (Reel 12, Frame 214)
    - Port of Oswego Authority (Reel 13, Frame 12)
    - Power Authority (Reel 13, Frame 14)
    - Preservation of Agriculture Land Commission (Reel 13, Frame 37)
    - Public Land and Review Commissions (Reel 13, Frame 46)
    - Pure Water Authority (Reel 13, Frame 60)
    - Revision of Penal Law (Reel 13, Frame 71)
    - Rochester & Genesee Regional Transit Authority (Reel 13, Frame 80)
    - Rochester - Monroe Port Authority (Reel 13, Frame 81)
    - Salamanca Hospital District Authority (Reel 13, Frame 87)
    - Science & Technology Foundation (Reel 13, Frame 95)
    - Social Development Planning Commission (Reel 13, Frame 123)
    - Suffolk County Human Relations Commission (Reel 13, Frame 156)
    - Suffolk County Water Authority (Reel 13, Frame 181)
    - Thousand Island Bridge Authority (Reel 13, Frame 186)
    - Thruway Authority (Reel 13, Frame 188)
    - Triborough Bridge & Tunnel Authority (Reel 14, Frame 11)
    - Waterfront Commission (Reel 14, Frame 32)
    - White Plains Parking Authority (Reel 14, Frame 58)
    - Yonkers Parking Authority (Reel 14, Frame 60)
    - A-Z (Reel 14, Frame 71)
    - General (Reel 14, Frame 182)
  - Banking (Reel 14, Reel 15)
    - Department of (Reel 14, Frame 188)
    - General
      - 1970 (Reel 14, Frame 218)
    - A-Z (Reel 14, Frame 240)
    - General, 1967-1969 (Reel 15, Frame 11)
  - Civil Defense (Reel 15)
    - Federal (Reel 15, Frame 65)
    - Civil Defense Commission (Reel 15, Frame 114)
    - Fallout Shelter Program (Reel 15, Frame 130)
    - General (Reel 15, Frame 148)
  - Commerce (Reel 15, Reel 16, Reel 17, Reel 18, Reel 19, Reel 20)
    - Aviation (Reel 15)
      - Airports (Reel 15)
        - Buffalo (Reel 15, Frame 152)
        - Jetports (Reel 15, Frame 157)
      - A-Z (Reel 15, Frame 214)
      - General (Reel 15, Frame 229)
    - Department of Business Promotion (Reel 16)
      - Conventions (Reel 16, Frame 14)
      - World Games Lake Placid (Reel 16, Frame 72)
      - General (Reel 16, Frame 91)
    - Department of Business Publicity (Reel 16, Reel 17)
      - 1970 (Reel 16, Frame 232)
      - 1967-1969 (Reel 17, Frame 11)
    - Department of Business Research (Reel 17, Frame 103)
    - Department of Business Service (Reel 17, Frame 148)
    - Radio, T.V. & Movie Productions (Reel 17, Reel 18)
      - N.A.R. Schedules & Transcripts (Reel 17, Frame 165)
      - Movie: "I am Curious Yellow" (Reel 17, Frame 176)
      - Television: "Issues and Answers" (Reel 17, Frame 179)
      - Television: "Today Show" (Reel 18, Frame 16)
      - Television: General (Reel 18, Frame 18)
    - Department of Commerce (Reel 18)
      - Science & Technology Foundation (Reel 18, Frame 117)
      - Travel (Reel 18, Frame 148)
      - Washington Office (Reel 18, Frame 149)
      - Women's Program (Reel 18, Frame 175)
      - Letters of Commendation (Reel 18, Frame 184)
      - General (Reel 18, Frame 191)
    - General (Reel 19, Reel 20)
      - Business Advisory Commission on Management Improvement (Reel 19)
      - Gypsum Plant at Little Stony Point (Reel 19)
      - Office of Planning Coordination (Reel 19)
      - Trans World Expo Japan (Reel 19)
      - World Trade Center Canada (Reel 19)
      - General
        - 1969 October-1970 October (Reel 19)
        - 1967 January-1969 September (Reel 20)
  - Conservation (Reel 20, Reel 21, Reel 22)
    - Department of (Reel 20)
      - Letters of Commendation (Reel 20)
      - Interstate Oil Compact Commission (Reel 20)
      - Land & Forest (Reel 20)
      - Division of Motor Boats (Reel 20)
      - New York City Historic Trust (Reel 20)
      - Park Commission (Reel 20)
    - Water Resources (Reel 20, Reel 21)
      - Delaware River Basin (Reel 20)
      - Great Lakes River Basin & Compact Commission (Reel 20)
      - New York State Water Resources Commission (Reel 20)
      - General
        - 1970 August-December (Reel 20)
        - 1967-1970 July (Reel 21)
    - Department of (Reel 21, Reel 22)
      - General (Reel 21, Reel 22)
        - 1969-1970 (Reel 21)
        - 1967-1968 (Reel 22)
    - General (Reel 22)
      - Beach Erosion (Reel 22)
      - Beautification Hometown Program (Reel 22)
      - Hudson River Valley Center (Reel 22)
      - Governor's Conference on Oceanography (Reel 22)
      - Oceanography (Reel 22)
      - General (Reel 22)
  - Consumer (Reel 22)
    - Problems of (Reel 22)
  - Correction (Reel 22, Reel 23)
    - Department of NYSILS (Reel 22)
    - General (Reel 22)
    - Institutions (Reel 22, Reel 23)
      - Attica
        - 1967-1970 (Reel 22)
        - 1967-1970 (Reel 23)
      - Auburn (Reel 23)
      - Dannemora (Reel 23)
      - Green Haven (Reel 23)
      - Mattewan (Reel 23)
      - Sing-Sing (Reel 23)
      - A-Z (Reel 23)
      - General (Reel 23)
    - Parole (Reel 23)
      - Division of Parole (Reel 23)
      - General (Reel 23)
  - Disaster (Reel 23, Reel 24)
    - Floods (Reel 23, Reel 24)
      - Allegany & Cattaraugus Counties (Reel 23)
      - Fire Island (Point of Woods), 1967-1968 (Reel 23)
      - Sullivan County (Reel 23)
      - Flood Control
        - 1961 (Reel 23)
        - 1967-1970 June (Reel 24)
    - Drought (Reel 24)
    - Snow (Reel 24)
    - Others (Reel 24)
    - General (Reel 24)
  - Discrimination (Reel 24, Reel 25)
    - Human Rights (Reel 24)
      - Division of Annual Reports (Reel 24)
      - General (Reel 24)
    - General (Reel 24)
      - Anti-Semitism (Reel 24)
    - Civil Rights (Reel 24)
      - Racial Imbalance (Reel 24)
      - General
        - 1967 August 19-1970 December (Reel 24)
        - 1967 January-August 18 (Reel 25)
    - Employment (Reel 25)
      - Minority Groups (Reel 25)
        - News Media (Reel 25)
        - State Service (Reel 25)
      - Minority Work Group (Reel 25)
        - Buffalo (Reel 25)
        - General (Reel 25)
        - General (Reel 25)
    - General (Reel 25)
      - Interdepartmental Commission on Human Rights (Reel 25)
      - Housing (Reel 25)
  - Education
    - Department of (Reel 25, Reel 26)
      - Board of Regents (Reel 25)
      - Commendations, Center of (Reel 26)
      - Vocational Rehabilitation (Reel 26)
      - General (Reel 26)
    - Finances (Reel 26, Reel 27, Reel 28)
      - Federal Aid (Reel 26)
      - State Aid
        - 1969 July-1970 December (Reel 26)
        - 1967 May 1-1969 June (Reel 27)
        - 1967 January-1967 May 1 (Reel 28)
      - General (Reel 28)
    - Museums and Historical Sites (Reel 28, Reel 29)
      - Albany Institute of History & Art (Reel 28)
      - American Museum of Natural History (Reel 28)
      - Gannagro Sites (Seneca Institue) (Reel 28)
      - Halfway House (Reel 28)
      - Huntington State (Reel 28)
      - Metropolitan Museum of Art (Reel 28)
      - Metropolitan Opera House (Reel 28)
      - Modern Art Museum (Reel 28)
      - Philadelphia Museum of Art (Reel 28)
      - Smithsonian Institut (Reel 28)
      - A-Z (Reel 28)
      - General (Reel 29)
    - Schools (Reel 29, Reel 30, Reel 31, Reel 32, Reel 33, Reel 34, Reel 35)
      - High & Elementary (Reel 29)
        - A-Z (Reel 29)
        - General (Reel 29)
      - Colleges & Universities (Reel 29, Reel 30, Reel 31, Reel 32, Reel 33, Reel 34)
        - Adelphi (Reel 29)
        - Albany (Reel 29)
        - Alfred (Reel 29)
        - American (Reel 29)
        - Amherst (Reel 29)
        - Binghamton (Reel 29)
        - Brandeis (Reel 29)
        - Brockport (Reel 29)
        - Brown (Reel 29)
        - Buffalo
          - 1970 April-September (Reel 29)
          - 1967 January-1970 March (Reel 30)
        - California (Reel 30)
        - Chicago (Reel 30)
        - Cincinnati (Reel 30)
        - City University (Reel 30)
        - Clarkson (Reel 30)
        - Cobleskill (Reel 30)
        - Colgate (Reel 30)
        - Columbia (Reel 30)
        - Cornell
          - 1969-1970 (Reel 30)
          - 1967-1968 (Reel 31)
        - Cortland (Reel 31)
        - Dartmouth (Reel 31)
        - Downtown Medical Center (Reel 31)
        - Farmington (Reel 31)
        - Florida Colleges A-Z (Reel 31)
        - Fordham (Reel 31)
        - Franklin-Essex Community College (Reel 31)
        - Fredonia (Reel 31)
        - Geneseo (Reel 31)
        - Hamilton (Reel 31)
        - Harvard (Reel 31)
        - Herkimer (Reel 31)
        - Hobart & William Smith (Reel 31)
        - Hofstra (Reel 31)
        - Hunter (Reel 31)
        - Illinois (Reel 31)
        - Iona (Reel 31)
        - Kentucky (Reel 31)
        - Long Island (Reel 31)
        - Louisville (Reel 31)
        - Maine (Reel 31)
        - Maritime (Reel 31)
        - Marymount (Reel 31)
        - Minnesota (Reel 31)
        - Monroe Community College (Reel 31)
        - Nassau Community College (Reel 31)
        - New Paltz (Reel 31)
        - New York University (Reel 32)
        - Niagara (Reel 32)
        - Northeastern (Reel 32)
        - Notre Dame (Reel 32)
        - Oneonta (Reel 32)
        - Oregon (Reel 32)
        - Oswego (Reel 32)
        - Pace (Reel 32)
        - University of Pennsylvania (Reel 32)
        - Plattsburgh (Reel 32)
        - Brooklyn Polytechnic Institute (Reel 32)
        - Princeton (Reel 32)
        - Queens (Reel 32)
        - Rensselaer Polytech Institute (Reel 32)
        - Saint Bonnaventure (Reel 32)
        - Skidmore (Reel 32)
        - Stonybrook (Reel 32)
        - Syracuse (Reel 32)
        - Institute of Technology(Rochester) (Reel 32)
        - Union (Reel 32)
        - Vassar (Reel 32)
        - Wake Forest (Reel 32)
        - Washington A-Z (Reel 32)
        - West Point (Reel 32)
        - Wisconsin (Reel 32)
        - Yale (Reel 32)
        - Yeshiva (Reel 32)
        - A-H (Reel 32)
        - I-Z (Reel 33)
        - General (Reel 33)
        - Campus Disorders
          - 1970 July (Reel 33)
          - 1970 July-August (Reel 34)
          - 1969 April-1970 June (Reel 34)
      - Other League Schools (Reel 34)
      - Others (Reel 34)
        - Lexington (Deaf) (Reel 34)
        - Life Skills (Reel 34)
        - A-H (Reel 34)
        - J-O (Reel 34)
        - P-Z (Reel 34)
      - State University (Reel 34, Reel 35)
        - State University: General (Reel 34)
        - Chancellors Panel on University Purposes, 1970 January-March (Reel 35)
        - Construction Fund (Reel 35)
        - Master Plan (Reel 35)
        - Proposed Colleges (Reel 35)
        - Scholarships (Reel 35)
        - Translations (Reel 35)
        - State University: General, 1970 April-December (Reel 35)
        - State University: General, 1967-1970 March (Reel 35)
    - General (Reel 35, Reel 36)
      - Adult Education (Reel 35)
      - Arts
        - Shakespeare Festival
          - 1970 June 21-July 30 (Reel 35)
          - 1970 June-July 20 (Reel 36)
        - Performing Arts (Reel 36)
          - Saratoga (Reel 36)
        - General Arts (Reel 36)
          - $18 Million App. (Reel 36)
          - Arts Council (Reel 36)
          - General (Reel 36)
            - Sara Deland (Reel 36)
            - General (Reel 36)
    - General (Reel 36, Reel 37)
      - Decentralization
        - 1970 (Reel 36)
        - 1967 March-1969 December (Reel 37)
      - Driver Education (Reel 37)
      - Education T.V. (Reel 37)
      - Education Commission of States (Reel 37)
      - Environmental Teach-In (Reel 37)
      - Government Commission Scholastic Achievement (Reel 37)
    - Higher Education (Reel 37, Reel 38)
      - Bundy Commission & Reports (Private Higher Education) (Reel 37)
      - Higher Education Assistance Corp (Reel 37)
      - Medical Education (Reel 37)
      - Tuition (Reel 37)
      - Scholar Incentive (Reel 37)
      - General
        - 1970 (Reel 37)
        - 1967 January-1969 December (Reel 38)
    - General (Reel 38, Reel 39)
      - Libraries (Reel 38, Reel 39)
        - New York Public (Reel 38)
        - A-Z (Reel 38)
        - Library Conference (Reel 38)
        - General (Reel 38)
        - Local Problems
          - New York City (Reel 38)
          - General (Reel 38)
            - 1968-1970 (Reel 38)
            - 1967 (Reel 39)
      - Head Start Program (Reel 39)
      - Retarded & Handicapped Children (Reel 39)
      - Pledge of Allegiance (Reel 39)
      - Seek Program (Reel 39)
      - Student Exchange (Reel 39)
      - Textbook Council Law (Reel 39)
      - Vocational Education (Reel 39)
      - General (Reel 39)
  - Environmental Conservation (Reel 39, Reel 40)
    - Department of (Reel 39)
    - General (Reel 40)
  - Executive Clemency (Reel 40)
    - Request for Forms (Reel 40)
    - Capital Punishment (Reel 40)
    - General (Reel 40)
  - Extradition (Reel 40)
    - General (Reel 40)
  - Fiscal (Reel 40, Reel 41, Reel 42, Reel 43, Reel 44)
    - Accounting & Auditing (Reel 40, Reel 41)
      - Audit & Control, Department of
        - 1968-1970 (Reel 40)
        - 1967 (Reel 41)
        - Audit Reports (Reel 41)
    - Budget (Reel 41, Reel 42)
      - Division of (Reel 41)
      - 1970-1971 Yearly Budget (Reel 41)
      - 1969-1970 Yearly Budget (Reel 41)
        - 1969 March 16-December (Reel 41)
        - 1969 January-March 15 (Reel 42)
      - 1967-1968 Yearly Budget (Reel 42)
    - Expenditures (Reel 42)
    - Tax & Finance (Reel 42)
      - Commendations (Reel 42)
      - Income Tax Bureau (Reel 42)
      - General (Reel 42)
      - Fees (Reel 42)
    - Taxation (Reel 42, Reel 43, Reel 44)
      - Cigarettes (Reel 42)
        - Cigarette Tax Conference (Reel 42)
        - Cigarette Tax (Reel 42)
      - Hotel Occupancy Tax (Reel 42)
      - Income Tax (Reel 42)
      - Lottery (Reel 42, Reel 43)
        - 1968-1970 (Reel 42)
        - 1967 (Reel 43)
      - Off-Track Betting (Reel 43)
      - Property Tax (Reel 43)
      - Sales Tax (Reel 43)
      - Stock Transfer (Reel 43)
      - Revenue Sharing (Reel 43)
      - Unincorporated Business Tax (Reel 43)
      - General (Reel 43, Reel 44)
        - 1968-1970 (Reel 43)
        - 1967 (Reel 44)
  - Fund Raising (Reel 44)
    - Arthritis (Reel 44)
    - Cancer (Reel 44)
    - Cerebral Palsy (Reel 44)
    - Community Chest Red Cross Fund (Reel 44)
    - Cystic Fibrosis (Reel 44)
    - Greater New York Fund (United Fund) (Reel 44)
    - Heart Fund (Reel 44)
    - Mental Health Appeal (Reel 44)
    - Multiple Sclerosis (Reel 44)
    - Muscular Dystrophy (Reel 44)
    - A-Z (Reel 44)
  - General Services (Reel 44)
    - Real Property Management (Reel 44)
      - Harlem Street Office Building (Reel 44)
      - Suffolk Street Office Building (Reel 44)
      - General (Reel 44)
      - Office of Central Operations (Reel 44)
        - State Cars (Reel 44)
        - General (Reel 44)
      - Office of Commendation (Reel 44)
      - Standards & Purchases (Reel 44)
        - General (Reel 44)
  - Government
    - Federal (Reel 44, Reel 45, Reel 46, Reel 47, Reel 48)
      - Advisory Commission on Intergovernmental Relations (Reel 44)
      - Agriculture, Department of (Reel 44)
      - Appalachian Regional Commission (Reel 45)
      - Atomic Energy Commission (Reel 45)
      - Commerce, Department of (Reel 45)
      - Defense Department (Reel 45)
      - Communications Commission (Reel 45)
      - Power Commission (Reel 45)
      - Health Education & Welfare (Reel 45)
      - Housing and Urban Development, Department of (Reel 45)
      - Inauguration
        - 1969 January 9-1970 (Reel 45)
        - 1967-1969 January 8 (Reel 46)
      - Interior, Department of (Reel 46)
      - Justice, Department of (Reel 46)
      - Labor, Department of (Reel 46)
      - Office of Economic Opportunity (OEO) (Reel 46)
      - Post Office, Department of (Reel 46)
      - President Office of Emergency Planning (Reel 46)
      - President Office of Nixon Administration (Reel 46)
      - President Office of Johnson Administration (Reel 47)
      - Small Business Administration (Reel 47)
      - State, Department of (Reel 47)
      - Transportation, Department of (Reel 47)
      - Treasury Department (Reel 47)
      - White House Fellows (Reel 47)
      - General
        - National Institute of Neurological Diseases & Illnesses (Reel 47)
        - General
          - 1969-1970 (Reel 47)
          - 1967-1968 (Reel 48)
    - International (Reel 48, Reel 49, Reel 50, Reel 51)
      - Asia (Reel 48)
      - Austria (Reel 49)
      - Belgium (Reel 49)
      - Biafra (Reel 49)
      - Brazil (Reel 49)
      - Canada (Reel 49)
      - Chile (Reel 49)
      - China (Reel 49)
      - Costa Rica (Reel 49)
      - Ecuador (Reel 49)
      - Ethiopia (Reel 49)
      - France (Reel 49)
      - Great Britain (Reel 49)
      - Greece (Reel 49)
      - India (Reel 49)
      - Indonesia (Reel 49)
      - Iran (Reel 49)
      - Israel (Reel 49)
      - Italy (Reel 49)
      - Jamaica (Reel 49)
      - Korea Latin (Reel 49)
      - Latin America (Reel 49)
        - 1970 (Reel 49)
      - Japan (Reel 49)
      - Latin America
        - 1969 June-December (Reel 49)
        - 1967-1969 May (Reel 50)
      - Liberia (Reel 50)
      - Middle East (Reel 50)